[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 19]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
♪ A meteor streaks
across the promises of the past ♪
♪ Memories wither at a touch ♪
♪ Seasons keep changing ♪
♪ I still remember your palm ♪
♪ Time has passed ♪
♪ The unexpectedly regret came to me ♪
It looks beautiful.
Isn't this too flashy?
♪ The warmth ♪
I'm afraid...
I knew you would say that.
♪ is still in my mind ♪
♪ At that time, happiness was too easy ♪
♪ We knew best how to waste it all ♪
♪ Before we learned to cherish it ♪
♪ We let each other slip away ♪
Just put it on
♪ The last time ♪
and then take it off right away.
Wouldn't that be a bad omen?
♪ I walked with you around some corner ♪
Do you still believe in these?
♪ A hug replaced all the outcomes ♪
♪ We both once had it all ♪
♪ This time we drifted apart ♪
Zhuo Yu'an
♪ Just don't forget me ♪
I'm sorry.
It didn't even cross my mind.
♪ The wind blew you and me apart ♪
I didn't get you anything.
It's okay.
♪ We once ran, cried,
and laughed together ♪
I'm here.
I've prepared everything.
♪ Walked all the way through
every twist and turn ♪
♪ Yet still missed each other
just as happiness drew near ♪
♪ Only after knowing what it is to lose ♪
♪ And never being able to touch again ♪
♪ Can we truly understand
what it means to have ♪
♪ We loved ♪
♪ Scattered and frozen
beneath the starry sky ♪
Hello?
Hello, Miss Shu.
Do you remember
the little black cat you rescued?
It's recovering very well now.
However,
there are others who want to adopt it now.
If you don't want to adopt it,
we will give it to a new owner.
Do I have to go there right now?
Yes.
Ah, yes.
You still have time if you come now.
Okay, I got it.
Okay.
You're really something.
Thanks, Mr. Zhou.
Next time, my treat.
Oh, it's no big deal.
She'll come pick you up later.
I'll stay with you.
But...
all this tonight...
There will be many more nights like this.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Why is it you?
Yi...
Muyang?
Yes.
The doctor had something come up,
so
I'm looking after the clinic for him.
The doctor just called me.
He said someone wants to adopt
the injured little black cat
I brought in earlier.
Yeah.
That's the one.
The little one's growing so fast.
When's the new owner coming?
Already here.
Could it be you?
That's great.
I'm relieved.
You trust me that much?
Yeah.
You look like
someone who really loves life.
And...
and have the ability to take good care of
other little lives.
Thank you.
By the way, I haven't asked you,
last time you...
I'm fine now.
If it's convenient for you,
could we exchange contact info?
I mean,
if you're willing,
you can share some updates
about the kitten with me.
Of course.
Great.
Let me add you on Wechat.
[Ding Ding Pet Hospital]
Okay.
Done.
Did you come alone?
Do you need me to give you a ride?
No, thanks.
Someone came with me.
The parking lot is full.
Later,
you might have to walk a bit more.
This is the kitten's new owner.
Hello.
Then we have to say goodbye.
You must grow up well.
It's such a pity.
We are both too busy
to take care of a new life.
We will have one in the future.
Who's this?
My husband.
Then,
please take good care of the kitten.
Okay.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Your mom doesn't want you anymore.
Let me take care of you from now on.
Zhuo Yu'an.
For now,
I don't want to make
our relationship public.
Okay.
Aren't you going to ask me why?
Then let me ask——
how does that gentleman know?
Because
he doesn't have much
overlap with our lives.
We have work dealings
and collaborations.
So it's better our colleagues
don't know about us.
Okay.
Your reasons,
I accept them all.
Well,
your family...
Will they...
They won't.
My father
is not easy to deal with.
It's actually better
if they don't know.
Zhuo Yu'an.
Thank you.
We separated too suddenly,
and met again by chance.
We can take our relationship slowly,
step by step.
Okay.
From now on, without your permission,
we will maintain
a pure relationship.
Really?
I can't.
Stop it.
Get some sleep.
You have a checkup tomorrow.
How can you sleep?
Shu Tinglan.
You're the one who said it first.
Looking at your results,
there are no more problems.
Your condition is much better
than before.
Have you had any interventions recently?
Actually,
my daily habits and pace
are pretty much the same as before.
I just moved.
Okay.
[Personal information Shu Tinglan]
[Test Result]
This is your last test report.
In fact,
you are psychologically healthy.
The reason you experienced
symptoms like auditory and
visual hallucinations
is because you
were subjected to unconscious hypnosis.
Once you leave that hypnotic environment,
the symptoms naturally disappear.
Hypnosis?
You said that in your work environment,
no one else experienced
similar situations.
So this problem
probably occurs
when you are alone.
Think carefully.
From when you first got sick
to your recent improvement—
have there been any changes
during this time?
Okay.
The door is fixed.
Thank you, sir.
Thanks for your hard work.
Did you think of anything?
No.
I'll observe more carefully
in my daily life.
Okay.
Miss Shu.
This matter can be serious or minor.
Hypnotizing someone
without their knowledge
is illegal.
You need to think about
how to handle this.
I heard your footsteps.
Why have you been standing at
the door for so long without coming in?
They are both getting anxious waiting.
You're finally back.
Mr. Zhuo made us wait for you to eat.
He wouldn't let me serve the food.
I'm starving.
Hey, Yu'an.
You and Shu Tinglan aren't being fair.
Getting married is such a big deal.
You think one home-cooked meal
is enough to brush us off?
It's enough that our friends know.
No need to be too flashy.
Alright, alright.
Anyway,
Shushu,
Mr. Zhuo,
Happy wedding!
Come on!